Absolutely, robots are the
big thing, right?
So robots have affected a
lot of other parts of
medicine,
but in shoulders and joints,
total hips and knees,
there's actually been not a
lot of science
to say robots are the next
panacea.
And we all think of going to
a surgeon that does robots,
It's a great marketing tool,
but ultimately you're not
solving a simple problem
and you're not adding
anything beneficial to the
patients.
From my side of therapy,
robotic procedures,
especially in the knee and
the hip,
and I've seen worse outcomes
than a doctor
that actually knows the
anomalies
where the robot knows
exactly what to do,
but it doesn't always know
what not to do.
Oh wow, that was a really
profound statement.
That's actually a modern
dilemma, right?